Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXIV is arranged in 5 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXV is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series LXVI is arranged in 14 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXIV. RITUAL
  - Sub-Series 383-0. Ritual
    - General, 1932 (Box 525, Folder 49)
    - General, 1925 (Box 525, Folder 50)
    - General, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 383-2. Ritual
    - Key to Secret Work, 1930-1948 (Box 525, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 383-3. Ritual
    - Union Label on Wearing Apparel, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 383-4. Ritual
    - Order of Business, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 383-5. Ritual
    - Obligation of Membership, 1932-1952 (Box 525, Folder 55)
- Series LXV. WAGE ARBITRATION
  - Sub-Series 384-0. Wage Arbitration
    - General, 1926-1929 (Box 525, Folder 56)
    - General, 1925-1926 (Box 525, Folder 57)
    - General, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 58)
    - General, 1925-1926 (Box 525, Folder 59)
    - General. United States Railroad Labor Board Statistical Bureau, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 60)
      1926 May 1
- Series LXVI. GRAND LODGE BOARD OF TRUSTEES
  - Sub-Series 385-0. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - General, 1932-1959 (Box 525, Folder 61)
    - General, 1928-1945 (Box 525, Folder 62)
    - General, 1930 (Box 525, Folder 63)
    - General, 1929 (Box 525, Folder 64)
    - General, 1927 (Box 525, Folder 65)
    - General, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 66)
    - General, 1925 (Box 525, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 385-2. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Meetings, 1928-1962 (Box 525, Folder 68)
    - Meetings, 1931 (Box 525, Folder 69)
    - Meetings, 1929 (Box 525, Folder 70)
    - Meetings, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 385-4. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Certified Public Accountant, 1932 (Box 525, Folder 72)
    - Certified Public Accountant, 1931 (Box 525, Folder 73)
    - Certified Public Accountant, 1929 (Box 525, Folder 74)
    - Certified Public Accountant, 1927 (Box 525, Folder 75)
    - Certified Public Accountant, 1926 (Box 525, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 385-6. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1933-1934 (Box 526, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1932 (Box 526, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1931 (Box 526, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1930 (Box 526, Folder 4)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1929 (Box 526, Folder 5)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1928 (Box 526, Folder 6)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1927 (Box 526, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 385-7. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Personnel, 1941-1959 (Box 526, Folder 8)
    - Personnel, 1929 (Box 526, Folder 9)
    - Personnel, 1925-1926 (Box 526, Folder 10)
    - Personnel, 1930 (Box 526, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 385-9. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Refunds to Grand Lodge, 1928 (Box 526, Folder 12)
    - Refunds to Grand Lodge, 1926 (Box 526, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 385-10. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Functions, 1926 (Box 526, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 385-11. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Budget, 1930 (Box 526, Folder 15)
    - Budget, 1926 (Box 526, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 385-12. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Special Meetings, 1927-1928 (Box 526, Folder 17)
    - Special Meetings, 1931 (Box 526, Folder 18)
    - Special Meetings, 1927 (Box 526, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 385-13. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Records, 1931 (Box 526, Folder 20)
    - Records, 1928-1929 (Box 526, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 385-14. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Activities, 1929 (Box 526, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 385-16. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Recommendations, 1936-1937 (Box 526, Folder 23)
    - Recommendations, 1932 (Box 526, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 385-17. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Scrip Railroad Mileage Books, 1933 (Box 526, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 385-18. Grand Lodge Board of Trustees
    - Per Diem and Mileage Allowances for Board Members, 1943-1947 (Box 526, Folder 26)